export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: "What does PoP stand for?",
    optionA: "Pre Office Protocol",
    optionB: "Post Office Protocol",
    optionC: "Protocol Of Post",
    optionD: "None",
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is the number of layers in the OSI model?",
    optionA: "2 layers",
    optionB: "4 layers",
    optionC: "7 layers",
    optionD: "9 layers",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Identify the layer which provides service to the user.",
    optionA: "Session layer",
    optionB: "Application layer",
    optionC: "Presentation layer",
    optionD: "Physical layer",
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is a HUB?",
    optionA: "Computing device",
    optionB: "Software",
    optionC: "Network device",
    optionD: "Calculating device",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Identify the full form of HTTP?",
    optionA: "HyperText Transfer Protocol",
    optionB: "HyperText Transfer Package",
    optionC: "Hyper Transfer Text Protocol",
    optionD: "Hyper Transfer Text Package",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Identify the first network which was based on TCP/IP protocol.",
    optionA: "ARPANET",
    optionB: "HUB",
    optionC: "Ethernet Card",
    optionD: "Router",
    answer: "optionA",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What does TCP/IP stand for?",
    optionA: "Telephone control protocol / Internet Protocol",
    optionB: "Transmission control protocol/Internet protocol",
    optionC: "Transmission control protocol/International protocol",
    optionD: "None",
    answer: "optionB",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is the collection of the hyperlinked document on the internet known as?",
    optionA: "HTML",
    optionB: "Email",
    optionC: "WWW",
    optionD: "Internet",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Identify the incorrect network topology,",
    optionA: "Bus",
    optionB: "Start",
    optionC: "P2P",
    optionD: "Ring",
    answer: "optionC",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What does MIME stand for?",
    optionA: "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extra",
    optionB: "Multi Internet Mail End",
    optionC: "Multipurpose Internet Mail Email",
    optionD: "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extension",
    answer: "optionD",
  },
];